<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">
  <properties>
    <title>brXM Discovery Plugin</title>
  </properties>
  <body>

    <section name="Alpha Notice">
      <p>
        <strong>&#9888; This plugin is in early-phase development (alpha).</strong>
        APIs, configuration schemas, HST component interfaces, and JCR node types are subject to change
        without notice between releases. Do not treat any aspect of this plugin as stable until a
        non-SNAPSHOT version is published to Bloomreach Forge.
      </p>
    </section>

    <section name="Introduction">
      <p>
        The brXM Discovery plugin integrates Bloomreach Discovery with brXM 16.7.0, providing CMS picker
        tooling, shared configuration resolution, CRISP-backed service clients, and HST components for
        search, category browse, recommendations, autosuggest, product detail, and pixel tracking.
      </p>
    </section>

    <section name="Module Overview">
      <table>
        <tr><th>Module</th><th>Purpose</th></tr>
        <tr>
          <td><strong>brxm-discovery-cms</strong></td>
          <td>CMS node types, picker REST endpoints, Open UI extensions, and Discovery bootstrap config.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><strong>brxm-discovery-site</strong></td>
          <td>Site runtime entry point: HST components, CRISP-backed clients, templates, and pixel service.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><strong>brxm-discovery-shared</strong></td>
          <td>Shared exceptions, configuration model, and request/query support used across runtimes.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><strong>brxm-discovery-hcm-site</strong></td>
          <td>Bundled HCM site bootstrap for the plugin's templates and HST resources.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><strong>demo</strong></td>
          <td>Standalone reference implementation showing the plugin wired into a runnable brXM project.</td>
        </tr>
      </table>
    </section>

    <section name="Getting Started">
      <ol>
        <li><a href="install.html">Install the plugin artifacts</a> into the CMS runtime and site runtime.</li>
        <li><a href="quick-start.html">Follow the quick start</a> to enable CRISP, add credentials, and wire a search page.</li>
      </ol>
    </section>

    <section name="Component Reference">
      <table>
        <tr><th>Page</th><th>Description</th></tr>
        <tr>
          <td><a href="search-category.html">Search &amp; Category</a></td>
          <td>Search and category browse data components, shared view components, and highlight components.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><a href="recommendations.html">Recommendations</a></td>
          <td>Widget-driven recommendation delivery, v1/v2 Pathways behaviour, and PDP band mode.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><a href="autosuggest.html">Autosuggest</a></td>
          <td>Inline typeahead behaviour exposed by <code>DiscoverySearchComponent</code>.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><a href="product-picker.html">Product Picker (CMS)</a></td>
          <td>CMS editor integrations for products, widgets, categories, and live category preview.</td>
        </tr>
      </table>
    </section>

    <section name="Configuration Reference">
      <table>
        <tr><th>Page</th><th>Description</th></tr>
        <tr>
          <td><a href="configuration.html">Discovery Configuration</a></td>
          <td>Global config node, structural defaults, channel overrides, CRISP spaces, and cache behaviour.</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
          <td><a href="credential-injection.html">Credential Injection</a></td>
          <td>Environment, system property, and JCR precedence with deployment guidance for secrets.</td>
        </tr>
      </table>
    </section>

  </body>
</document>
