<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">
  <properties>
    <title>Product Picker (CMS)</title>
  </properties>
  <body>

    <section name="Alpha Notice">
      <p>
        <strong>&#9888; This plugin is in early-phase development (alpha).</strong>
        APIs, configuration schemas, HST component interfaces, and JCR node types are subject to change
        without notice between releases. Do not treat any aspect of this plugin as stable until a
        non-SNAPSHOT version is published to Bloomreach Forge.
      </p>
    </section>

    <section name="What it provides">
      <p>
        The picker runtime is an Open UI document field extension embedded inside the brXM CMS editor. It
        lets editors search Discovery data visually and store product IDs, widget IDs, or category IDs in
        document fields without exposing Discovery credentials to the browser.
      </p>
    </section>

    <section name="REST endpoint reference">
      <table>
        <tr><th>Endpoint</th><th>Purpose</th></tr>
        <tr><td><code>/search</code></td><td>Search products for the product picker dialog.</td></tr>
        <tr><td><code>/items</code></td><td>Resolve one or more specific product IDs.</td></tr>
        <tr><td><code>/categories</code></td><td>Return the Discovery category tree.</td></tr>
        <tr><td><code>/browse</code></td><td>Browse products within a category.</td></tr>
        <tr><td><code>/widgets</code></td><td>List available recommendation widgets.</td></tr>
        <tr><td><code>/category-products</code></td><td>Return preview products for an editor-selected category.</td></tr>
      </table>
    </section>

    <section name="Category product preview">
      <p>
        <code>discoveryCategoryProductPreview</code> is the inline companion field used by the category
        picker flow. It stores a thumbnail count, listens for category changes via <code>postMessage</code>,
        and reloads preview products immediately without waiting for a document save.
      </p>
    </section>

    <section name="Linking a document field">
      <div class="brush: yaml">
        <source><![CDATA[
/my-product-ref:
  jcr:primaryType: frontend:plugin
  caption: 'Featured Product'
  field: 'myns:productId'
  plugin.class: 'org.onehippo.cms7.frontend.plugin.field.OpenUiStringFieldPlugin'
  uiExtension: 'discoveryProductPicker'
  wicket.id: '${cluster.id}.field'
        ]]></source>
      </div>
    </section>

    <section name="Troubleshooting">
      <table>
        <tr><th>Symptom</th><th>Likely cause</th></tr>
        <tr><td>Picker iframe is blank</td><td><code>brxm-discovery-cms</code> is missing or the daemon module did not start.</td></tr>
        <tr><td>Field value disappears after save</td><td>The property was not declared in the document type definition.</td></tr>
        <tr><td>Preview thumbnails do not follow category changes</td><td>The category picker and preview field are not rendered as same-origin sibling iframes.</td></tr>
      </table>
    </section>

  </body>
</document>
